Open the Prentice Files file at the window of the picture.
Find the eFixition.a Simulation Instability the Entire Gamut file.
Drag it to the 2D or 3D window.
After the fire simulation, the panels will collide with each other immediately, causing the costume to move continuously.
This is because the panel is not in the correct position when it is arranged.
In the 3D window, select Rearrange 3D Arrangement, All.
In the 3D window, the panels will be remodeled before the simulation.
In the 2D window, select the front panel panel.
In the 3D window, right-click and select Rearrange 2D Position Arrangement.
Select the 2D arrangement of the front panel to the 3D window.
In the 3D window, right-click on the panel.
Left-click to select the positional ball.
Use the quick arrangement tool to arrange the panels to the front panel.
Use the positional ball tool to arrange the panels to the inside of the panel.
Repeat the operation on the other side.
Place the panels behind the front panel panel.
In the 2D window, select the right-front panel and the right-front panel panel.
In the 3D window, use the positional ball tool.
Place the right-front panel to the top of the left-front panel.
Rotate the view to see the distance between the panels.
Open the arrangement point.
In the 2D window, select the front panel panel.
In the front window arrangement point, click to put the panel down.
In the 2D window, select the outer panel panel.
In the 3D window, use the positional ball tool to drag the outer panel away from the inner panel.
Rotate the view to see the distance between the panels.
In the 2D window, select the outer panel of the lower right panel.
In the 3D window, use the positional ball tool to drag the panel away from the left panel.
Rotate the view to see the distance between the panels.
Activate the simulation.
Check if the clothing can be stabilized.
Turn off the simulation.